A Guide to the Charles Veatch Collection
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University Libraries
The Charles Veatch Collection
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Veatch 001
14 boxes comprising 4.6 cubic feet or 6.9 linear feet
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Collection was acquired from Mr. Charles A. Veatch in 2004.
Biographical/Historical Information
Charles A. Veatch was born in 1942 in Washington, DC. He obtained his B.S. in Finance from the University of Virginia in 1964. During the summer of 1964, he began working for Palindrome Corporation under Robert E. Simon, the developer of Reston, Virginia, and in 1968 moved to Reston with his wife and two children. Veatch obtained his real estate license in 1960, while still a student at UVA. He started his own real estate development and consulting firm, Environmental Concepts, Inc., in 1970. He soon developed many residential and commercial projects throughout Northern Virginia, including ones in Reston.
For decades, Veatch has been an avid participant in Reston community organizations. During the early days of Reston, he was a founding member of the Reston Lions Club and the Reston Board of Commerce. He is currently a member of numerous nonprofit boards including Planned Community Archives, Reston Historic Trust, Greater Reston Arts Center, Natures Best Foundation, The Potomac Conservancy, and Fairfax County Parks Foundation. Furthermore, he has many other affiliations with nonprofit organizations such as the Friends of Shenandoah River, Friends of North Fork, and The French and Indian War Foundation. Veatch has been honored with many awards for his extensive community service. In 1998 he was named the Best of Reston Honoree, and in 2004 he was chosen as the Fairfax County Citizen of the Year.
As a fly fisherman and lover of nature, Veatch began photographing the scenes around him. Now a passionate and accomplished photographer, Veatch published The Nature of Reston in 1999, a book of his photography of natural areas of Reston. Profits from this book, now in its second printing, have gone towards the construction of a Nature House in Reston. Currently, Charles Veatch is the president of The Charles A. Veatch Co. He also devotes his time to many nonprofit organizations concerned with nature and the environment.
Scope and Content
Collection contains materials pertaining to the history and development of Reston, Virginia. Types of materials include: newspaper and magazine clippings pertaining to Reston. photographs and negatives of structures in Reston, reports regarding Reston planning issues, video recordings, promotional materials regarding Reston attractions such as Reston Town Center, records pertaining to Planned Community Archives, Inc. and other materials.
Arrangement
By subject.
Contents List
- The Charles Veatch Collection
  - RLC Clips. Sept 1985 Including Builder's House, Folder 1 (Box Box 1)
  - RLC Clips - August 1985, Folder 2 (Box Box)
  - Birthday Party Orders (Delivered and Paid For), Folder 3 (Box Box 1)
  - Peter McCandless - RLC Clips July 1985, Folder 4 (Box Box 1)
  - RLC Clips May/June 1985, Folder 5 (Box Box 1)
  - RLC Clips May 1985, Folder 6 (Box Box 1)
  - National Clips, Folder 7 (Box Box 1)
  - RLC Clips April/May 1985, Folder 8 (Box Box 1)
  - RLC Clips March 1985, Folder 1 (Box Box 2)
  - he Veatch Collection - RLC Clips April 1985, Folder 2 (Box Box 2)
  - RLC Clips January - February 1985, Folder 3 (Box Box 2)
  - RLC Clips January 1985, Folder 4 (Box Box 2)
  - RLC Clips December 1984 (1 Of 2), Folder 5 (Box Box 2)
  - RLC Clips December 1984 (1 Of 2), Folder 6 (Box Box 2)
  - RLC Clips November 1984, Folder 1 (Box Box 3)
  - RLC Clips October 1984 (1 of 2), Folder 2 (Box Box 3)
  - RLC Clips October 1984 (2 of 2), Folder 3 (Box Box 3)
  - RLC Clips Late August 1984, Folder 4 (Box Box 3)
  - RLC Clips September 1984, Folder 5 (Box Box 3)
  - RLC Clips June/July 1984, Folder 6 (Box Box 3)
  - RLC Clips July/August 1984, Folder 7 (Box Box 3)
  - Phase II Land Use Report, Folder 1 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Phase II Land Use Report, Folder 2 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 1999/2000 Task Force Recommendations, Folder 3 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Report to the Community, Folder 4 (Box Box 4)
  - Task Force Transparency Slides, Folder 5 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Land Use Committee Recommendations, Folder 6 (Box Box 4)
  - Material For My Request, Folder 7 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Executive Summary: Report of the Land Use, Community Development and Revitalization Committee 9/14/98, Folder 8 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Reports, Folder 9 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - Vision Statement/Goals for Land Use, Community Development and Revitalization Committee, Folder 10 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - Hickory Cluster Common Area Improvement Study, Folder 11 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - Contributions to Report of Reston 2000 Land Use Committee, Folder 12 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - Transportation Committee July 30, 1998, Folder 13 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - Reston Mater Plan - October 1, Folder 14 (Box Box 4)
  - Goals for LUCDC, Folder 15 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Fairfax Economic Advisory Board Commission Meeting Minutes for March 17, 1997, Folder 16 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Proposed Commercial Revitalization Initiatives, Folder 17 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Land Use + CD Commission Evaluation, Goals + Ideas, Folder 18 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - Reston Town Center Urban Design Principles 2/91, Folder 19 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 Committee Members Information (Address, Phone #), Folder 20 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - July 13, 1999 Meeting on Transportation Finance, Folder 21 (Box Box 4)
  - Reston 2000 - Dulles Corridor Rail System Planning, Folder 1 (Box Box 5)
  - Reston 2000 - Reston on Foot - Revised 1999, Folder 2 (Box Box 5)
  - Reston 2000 Corridor Rapid Transit Project: Summary of Findings May 1999, Folder 3 (Box Box 5)
  - Reston 2000 Task Force Responsibilities and Work Plan Phase II Implementation, Folder 4 (Box Box 5)
  - Reston 2000 Final Report for Land Use, Community Development, and Revitalization Committee, Folder 5 (Box Box 5)
  - Reston 2000 - Phase II Reston Assoc. Report on Implementing Task Force Goals + Objectives - November 1999, Folder 6 (Box Box 5)
  - Planned Community Archives Finding Aid with Index- 1994 SPC + A, Folder 7 (Box Box 5)
  - Map of Reston, Virginia, Folder 8 (Box Box 5)
  - Brochure for Charles A. Veatch Company, Folder 9 (Box Box 5)
  - Reston Property Taxes Exceed $2 Million in FY71, Folder 10 (Box Box 5)
  - Correspondence Regarding Various Actions to Offset and Direct Public School and Education Expense in New Communities, Folder 11 (Box Box 5)
  - 1972 Correspondence Regarding Virgina Tech's New Communities Study Center, Folder 12 (Box Box 5)
  - RLC 260 -91\ Milne, Folder 13 (Box Box 5)
  - Mobil Gift to Child $500/Mercury Fountain/RLC 261-91, Folder 14 (Box Box 5)
  - Mobil Gift to PCA/Gullfoy le/RLC 262 - 91, Folder 15 (Box Box 5)
  - Mobil Foundation Gift to YMCA/RLC 263-91, Folder 16 (Box Box 5)
  - RLC 3X A WINNER at 1990 Mame RLC 264-91, Folder 17 (Box Box 5)
  - Benton Promoted to Proj.Mgr.Col Village RLC 265-91, Folder 18 (Box Box 5)
  - Mobil Foundation Gift to Grace RLC 266-91, Folder 19 (Box Box 5)
  - Mobil Foundation/Reston Players RLC 269-91 October 1991, Folder 20 (Box Box 5)
  - W and OD Trail Improvement $2.5 Million RLC 238-90, Folder 21 (Box Box 5)
  - Key Corp Changes/D'Alesandro RLC 226-89 9/20/89, Folder 22 (Box Box 5)
  - Schmergel Joins RLC Marketing RLC 230-89, Folder 23 (Box Box 5)
  - Schultz + Guilfoyle Promotions, Folder 1 (Box Box 6)
  - RLC Clips August 1996, Folder 2 (Box Box 6)
  - RLC Clips December 1986 (1 of 2), Folder 3 (Box Box 6)
  - RLC Clips December 1986 (2 of 2), Folder 4 (Box Box 6)
  - RLC Clips November 1986, Folder 5 (Box Box 6)
  - The Washington Flyer October 1985, Folder 6 (Box Box 6)
  - RLC Clips October 1986 (1 of 2), Folder 7 (Box Box 6)
  - RLC Clips October 1986 (2 of 2), Folder 1 (Box Box 7)
  - RLC Clips September 1986, Folder 2 (Box Box 7)
  - RLC Clips July - August 1986, Folder 3 (Box Box 7)
  - RLC Clips July 1986, Folder 4 (Box Box 7)
  - RLC Clips June 1986, Folder 5 (Box Box 7)
  - RLC Clips May 1986, Folder 1 (Box Box 8)
  - RLC Clips April 1986, Folder 2 (Box Box 8)
  - RLC Clips March/April 1986, Folder 3 (Box Box 8)
  - RLC Clips February/March 1986, Folder 4 (Box Box 8)
  - RLC Clips Town Center Masters 2/18/86, Folder 5 (Box Box 8)
  - RLC Clips (Masters) Mid - Jan to Mid - Feb 1986, Folder 6 (Box Box 8)
  - RLC Clips January 1986, Folder 1 (Box Box 9)
  - RLC Clips December 1985, Folder 2 (Box Box 9)
  - RLC Clips September/October 1985, Folder 3 (Box Box 9)
  - RLC Clips October/November 1985, Folder 4 (Box Box 9)
  - RLC Clips November 1985, Folder 5 (Box Box 9)
  - RLC Clips September 1985, Folder 6 (Box Box 9)
  - The Nature of Reston - Reston Historic Trust and Brochure, Folder 7 (Box Box 9)
  - Mater Plan of Reston - Reston Land Corporation, October 1988, Folder 8 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Information Providers - Tour of Reston March 8, 1989, Folder 9 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston 1987 - Insert 1989 Newsletter, Folder 10 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston at a Glance - 1989, Folder 11 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Land Corporation - Development in Reston, VA, Folder 12 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Market Profile: Population, Folder 13 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Market Profile: Community Services, Folder 14 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Market Profile: Schools, Folder 15 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Market Profile: Transportation, Folder 16 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Town Center Project Description, Folder 17 (Box Box 9)
  - 1989 Facts: Business + Industry in Reston, Folder 18 (Box Box 9)
  - 1989 Facts: Residential Reston, Folder 19 (Box Box 9)
  - 1989 Facts: Recreational Reston, Folder 20 (Box Box 9)
  - Reston Press Conference - July 21, 1970, Folder 1 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Section Maps, Folder 2 (Box Box 10)
  - Statistical Synopsis on Housing and Land Use, Folder 3 (Box Box 10)
  - Upcoming Housing Construction in Reston, Folder 4 (Box Box 10)
  - Cedar Ridge Apartment Layouts, Folder 5 (Box Box 10)
  - Regency Square Townhouse Layouts, Folder 6 (Box Box 10)
  - The Bridges of Reston Layouts, Folder 7 (Box Box 10)
  - Bryan Courts Houses Layouts, Folder 8 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston's Fairfield Home Layout, Folder 9 (Box Box 10)
  - Planned Community Archives Brochure, Folder 10 (Box Box 10)
  - CAV Reston Board of Commerce Meetings 1983-87, Folder 11 (Box Box 10)
  - A Child Looks at Reston, Folder 12 (Box Box 10)
  - Photographs of Veach with Colleagues In Front of satellite Dish, Folder 13 (Box Box 10)
  - PCA - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors January 19, 1989, Folder 14 (Box Box 10)
  - PCA Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Directors, May 15 1990, Folder 15 (Box Box 10)
  - PCA Financial Statements - March 31,1990 and 1989, Folder 16 (Box Box 10)
  - Rev. Reagan With His Daughter - Reston's First Baby, Folder 17 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Root Beer 40 Years Logo, Folder 18 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Town Center Map - 1990, Folder 19 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Child Care - 1990, Folder 20 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Commercial Real Estate - Spring 1990, Folder 21 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Arts - 1990, Folder 22 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Business - 1990, Folder 23 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Transportation - 1990, Folder 24 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Amenities - 1990, Folder 25 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Commercial Real Estate - 1990, Folder 26 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Master Plan - October 1988 Map, Folder 27 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Neighborhoods - 1990, Folder 28 (Box Box 10)
  - Link New Ideas Transportation For Reston - 1990, Folder 29 (Box Box 10)
  - JR Davidon's Reston Land Corporation Business Card - 1990, Folder 30 (Box Box 10)
  - Planning, July 1990: p.22 Pumping Up Suburban Downtowns, Folder 31 (Box Box 10)
  - A Straight foreward Message from: Gulf Oil Real Estate Development Company, Folder 32 (Box Box 10)
  - Northern Va. NAIOP 1997 Fall Bus Tour (Guidebook), Folder 33 (Box Box 10)
  - Outline of Reston Apartments, Folder 34 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Multi Family Building Programs 1972-74, Folder 35 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Estate Booklet "Reston: Far Out But Close In, Folder 36 (Box Box 10)
  - Harbor side Patio Homes Floor Plans and Features, Folder 37 (Box Box 10)
  - Introducing the Easiest Way in Washington to Earn Your 3%, Folder 38 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Realtors Tour Map, Folder 39 (Box Box 10)
  - A History of Reston Virgina's Unique Community, Folder 40 (Box Box 10)
  - In Reston, Your Association Can Enjoy the Advantages of Washington Without Suffering the Disadvantages, Folder 41 (Box Box 10)
  - The Walden Layouts, Folder 42 (Box Box 10)
  - Reston Master Plan - 1971, Folder 43 (Box Box 10)
  - The Atrium System, Folder 44 (Box Box 10)
  - Just Outside the Nations Capital is One of the Best Neighborhoods In America, Folder 45 (Box Box 10)
  - Site Plan (Unidentified Location), Folder 1 (Box Box 11)
  - Bowman Green - Office Town houses Brochure, Folder 2 (Box Box 11)
  - Lake Audubon Terrace Patio Homes Layout, Folder 3 (Box Box 11)
  - The Village of Southlake - maps, Folder 4 (Box Box 11)
  - Whitney Park. Great Townhouses Bordering the Great Outdoors, Folder 5 (Box Box 11)
  - Presenting Reston's 1979 Advertising Program, Folder 6 (Box Box 11)
  - Design of the "Conceptual House" Hugh Newell Jacobsen, Folder 7 (Box Box 11)
  - Reston Development Plan - April 1979, Folder 8 (Box Box 11)
  - Description of Reston, VA Images Collection at GMU Libraries, Folder 9 (Box Box 11)
  - Reston Historic Trust for Community Revitalization - 1997, Folder 10 (Box Box 11)
  - Invitation to the Celebration of Reston's 50000th Citizen on Nov, 1987, Folder 11 (Box Box 11)
  - Chuck Veatch: Citizen of the Year 2000 Newspaper Clip, Folder 12 (Box Box 11)
  - Article From the Washington Post, Folder 13 (Box Box 11)
  - Article From the Washington Post Magazine: City of Life, Folder 14 (Box Box 11)
  - Greater Reston Guide Book 2002 Edition, Folder 15 (Box Box 11)
  - Reston Park Brochures, Folder 16 (Box Box 11)
  - New Dominion Magazine: Reston New Possibilities. From Urban Living to Virginia's Second Largest Business Center, Folder 17 (Box Box 11)
  - Lakewinds Housing Collection, Folder 18 (Box Box 11)
  - Reston Association - Design Guidelines and Design Review Process, 2nd Edition 1990, Folder 19 (Box Box 11)
  - The Best of Northern Virginia - 1990 Reston Land Corporation, Folder 20 (Box Box 11)
  - 1992 Newspaper Clips From March 23 - April 21, Folder 21 (Box Box 11)
  - 1992 Newspaper Clips From March 1- 23, Folder 22 (Box Box 11)
  - Negative Sheet and Negative of Reston Homes, Folder 1 (Box Box 12)
  - Reston: Unlike the Rest - Posters, Folder 2 (Box Box 12)
  - Reston Town Center - Detailed Booklet, Folder 3 (Box Box 12)
  - 1990 Reston Land Corporation - Map of Washington/Fairfax Area, Folder 4 (Box Box 12)
  - Washington Post Fairfax Extra 3/24/04: A Vision Still Strong As Ever, Folder 5 (Box Box 12)
  - Reston Connection Jan 28 - Feb 3 2004 - Millions for Watershed, Folder 6 (Box Box 12)
  - The Veach Collection - The Washington Post METRO - Sunday 4/18/04: Bamboo Brigade, Folder 7 (Box Box 12)
  - The Reston Times - Wed 4/21/04: Founders Day April 17, 2004, Folder 8 (Box Box 12)
  - Reston Connection - April 21-27,2004 :Tis His Day, Folder 9 (Box Box 12)
  - The Business Review Pull - Out Week of May 6 - 10, 1985 pages 21-36, Folder 10 (Box Box 12)
  - A Souvenir Supplement of the Connection - May 15, 1985, Folder 11 (Box Box 12)
  - The Energy Efficient Community of the Future Isn't That Far Away (POSTER), Folder 12 (Box Box 12)
  - Reston Celebrating It's 20th Year! Special Issue of the Reston Times, May 16, 1985, Folder 13 (Box Box 12)
  - Reston Virginia Home Owner's Kit Plastic Zipper Bag, Folder 14 (Box Box 12)
  - One of the 15 Best Places to Live inn America is Right Here In Washington (POSTER), Folder 15 (Box Box 12)
  - Reston Times - Wednesday, January 5, 2000, Folder 16 (Box Box 12)
  - Times Community Newspapers - 1/15/00 Page All, Folder 17 (Box Box 12)
  - King Charles Commons Layouts, Folder 18 (Box Box 12)
  - Newspaper Clips - 1992, Folder 19 (Box Box 12)
  - Articles of Incorporation New Town Archives, Inc - Daft - 2/15/85, Folder 1 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence From Peter McCandless To Ted Schelzer about PCA, Folder 2 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence Regarding Robert Hide's Book, Folder 3 (Box Box 13)
  - A Letter From Tom Grubisich Regarding PCA Welcome to Reston, Folder 4 (Box Box 13)
  - Memorandum of Understanding With PCA, Folder 5 (Box Box 13)
  - Budget for 20th Anniversary Celebration Committee, Folder 6 (Box Box 13)
  - Estimated Manufacturing Costs for Reston: The first 20 Years, April 2, 1985, Folder 7 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA Interim Budget, April 4 - June 30, 1985, Folder 8 (Box Box 13)
  - Memo of Intent Approved by the Board of PCA, Folder 9 (Box Box 13)
  - Deed of Gift from Thomas Grubisich and Peter McCandless To Planned Community Archives. Inc - March 19, 1985, Folder 10 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA - A District of Columbia Non Profit Corporation: Minutes of Organizational Meeting of the Board of Directors, April 3, 1985, Folder 11 (Box Box 13)
  - Bylaws of Planned Community Action Inc. - As Adopted April 13, 1985, Folder 12 (Box Box 13)
  - Bylaws of New Town Archives, Inc. - Draft of Feb. 15, 1985, Folder 13 (Box Box 13)
  - Archives Development Grant Recommendation 6/1/87, Folder 14 (Box Box 13)
  - Agreement and Beneficial Deed Between GMU and PCA - 4/21/87, Folder 15 (Box Box 13)
  - GMU Acquires Community Development Archives - April 21, 1987, Folder 16 (Box Box 13)
  - Partnership with George Mason University Announced - Reston Collection Anchors 1st Kind of Archive - Sept 9, 1987, Folder 17 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA: Summary of Objectives and Activities, Folder 18 (Box Box 13)
  - Planned Community Archives - Addresses of Officers, Folder 19 (Box Box 13)
  - Planned Comm. Archives: High School Curriculum, Folder 20 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence Welcoming William C. Pflaum CO. To Reston, Folder 21 (Box Box 13)
  - Urban Land Institute 1986 Publications Catalog, Folder 22 (Box Box 13)
  - Draft Deed of Gift, Folder 23 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA Grant Proposal, April 23, 1992, Folder 24 (Box Box 13)
  - p.38 May 86/ Urban Land: Anew Community Passes the Endurance Test, Folder 25 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence to Librarian About " Reston: The First 20 Years" Book, Folder 26 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence RSVP To Reston's 25th Anniversary Celebration, Folder 27 (Box Box 27)
  - PCA'S Letter Agreement With WETA, Folder 28 (Box Box 13)
  - The Reston Forum Letter To Veatch To Join A Task Force 11/25/87, Folder 29 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence Regarding Dean Coleman Raphael and PCA/GMU "Strategy For Future Operations", Folder 30 (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation To Bill Nicoson and Ernie Berger To Attend A Meeting June 6, From 1-3 1998, Folder 31 (Box Box 13)
  - Memo Regarding Future Strategy for GMU PCA Collaborators, Folder 32 (Box Box 13)
  - Outline of Proposed GMU Certificate Program in Urban + Suburban Studies, Folder 33 (Box Box 13)
  - Peter McCandless Notes, Folder 34 (Box Box 13)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Draft of 3/19/85, Folder 35 (Box Box 13)
  - Letter to PCA 1 Regarding Payment of Books from the Memo of Understanding With PCA Dated 4/25/85, Folder 36 (Box Box 13)
  - To: Directors of PCA Welcoming to Reston Planned Community From: Tom Gruibisich, Folder 37 (Box Box 13)
  - Invitation to Gregory J. Friess to Join the Board of PCA 6/30/85, Folder 38 (Box Box)
  - New Community Archives, Inc. Possible New Archives 8/22/85, Folder 39 (Box Box 13)
  - Marketing Report + Book Inventory Sales, Folder 40 (Box Box 13)
  - Marketing Strategies to Date [1985], Folder 41 (Box Box 13)
  - Proposals to PCA Board Members About Establishing A Relationship With GMU 11/19/85, Folder 42 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence Regarding Future Plans of A Performing Arts Center In Reston. 4/4/86, Folder 43 (Box Box)
  - Urban Land: Sprucing Up A Specialty Center - May' 86, Folder 44 (Box Box 44)
  - Coming Soon: Greenbelt's 50th Anniversary, Folder 45 (Box Box 13)
  - Correspondence Regarding Important New Tax Info. 5/26/86, Folder 46 (Box Box 13)
  - Proposal For University Course In Urban Planning, June 1986 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA Budget - Year Ending March 31, 1987, Folder 48 (Box Box 13)
  - Financial Statements - March 31, 1988, Folder 49 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA Financial Statements from March 31, 1986-87, Folder 50 (Box Box 13)
  - Corresponding Thanking Veatch For Speaking In Commercial Property Development and Management Class At GMU 10/7/86, Folder 51 (Box Box 13)
  - Walking A Financial Tightrope - Land Use Policy, Folder 52 (Box Box 13)
  - Land Use Policy - Vol.4 NO.1 1/1987, Folder 53 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA Summary of Objectives and Activities, Folder 54 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA - Action by Consent of the Board of Directors, Folder 55 (Box Box 13)
  - PCA - GMU Agreement + Beneficial Deed Draft of 12/22/86, Folder 56 (Box Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence from Veatch, Folder 57 (Box Box 13)
  - Silver Anniversary Planning, Folder 58 (Box Box 13)
  - Postcard to Veach, Folder 59 (Box Box 13)
  - Invoice No. 1001 - For PCA, Folder 1 (Box Box 14)
  - Agreement Between PCA and Warner Cable of Reston, Folder 2 (Box Box 14)
  - Correspondence Regarding Mutual Use Network of Sources For Sharing of Records In Development Projects, Folder 3 (Box Box 14)
  - PCA - History + Current Activities, Archival Development, Educational Projects, Folder 4 (Box Box 14)
  - Letter of Recommendation For John Mathias To Serve On Board of Directors in PCA, Folder 5 (Box Box 14)
  - Planned Community Archives: Its Collection At George Mason University and Its Educational Projects, Folder 6 (Box Box 14)
  - Inside ULI Vol No. 1 Spring 1989, Folder 7 (Box Box 14)
  - Oral History: 9 Points To Consider For A Good Interview, Folder 8 (Box Box 14)
  - Deed of Gift to the Oral History of the Planned Community Archives, Special Collections and Archives, Folder 9 (Box Box 14)
  - PCA Brochure On Its Collection At GMU, Folder 10 (Box Box 14)
  - PCA Financial Statements March 31, 1990 and 1989, Folder 11 (Box Box 14)
  - An Agreement and Beneficial Order, Folder 12 (Box Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Folder 13 (Box Box 14)
  - The Accents on International Business: Fairfax County, Virginia, Folder 14 (Box Box 14)
  - 1998 World Congress on Information Technology XI, Folder 15 (Box Box 14)
  - Economy: Fairfax, Virginia 1995, Folder 16 (Box Box 14)
  - Demographics:Fairfax Country, Virginia, 1995, Folder 17 (Box Box 14)
  - Education: Fairfax County, Virginia 1995, Folder 18 (Box Box 14)
  - Housing: Fairfax County, Virginia 1995, Folder 19 (Box Box 14)
  - Quality of Life: Fairfax County, Virginia 1995, Folder 20 (Box Box 14)
  - Business Report Fairfax County Economic Development Authority: Year End 1995 Real Estate Market Review 1995 Retail Report, Folder 21 (Box Box 14)
  - Major Employers: Fairfax County, Virginia 1996-97, Folder 22 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax Prospectus Second Quarter 1996, Folder 23 (Box Box 14)
  - Destination Fairfax County, Virginia May/June 1996, Folder 24 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax County, Virginia Economic Development Authority Services (Brochure), Folder 25 (Box Box 14)
  - Fairfax County, Virginia Economic Development Authority Homepage, Folder 26 (Box Box 14)
  - 40 Years - 1995 Annual Report - Fairfax County Economic Development Authority, Folder 27 (Box Box 14)
  - Business Report - Merrifield Area Market Report by the Fairfax County Economic Development Authority 1994, Folder 28 (Box Box 14)